(Sheldon:)- By lying to them?
- How is this lying?
(Sheldon:)A magic show is an inherently
deceitful proposition.
"This is an ordinary top hat."
"You've chosen that card freely."
"l do not have a set
of lock picks lodged in my keister."
Can't you just enjoy the wonder?
(Raj:)Why must you peek
behind the curtain, or up the butt?
(Sheldon:)If we poison the critical thinking
facuIties of children...
(Sheldon:)...by telling them
rabbits come out of hats...
...then we create aduIts who believe
in astrology and homeopathy...
...and Ryan Reynolds was a
better choice for Green Lantern...
(Sheldon:)...than lovable rogue Nathan Fillion.
(Leonard:)He's just gonna do
a few magic tricks for some kids.
(Leonard:)I really don't think they're gonna
end up liking the Green Lantern movie.
(Howard:)Don't be so hard on him, it's natural
to be a little cranky when you have...
(Howard:)...a quarter in your ear.
(Sheldon:)Coins lodged in body parts
is not a source of amusement.
(Sheldon:)When I was five, Billy Sparks
put a Mexican peso up my nose.
- How is that not amusing?
- It's still there.
It takes me 45 minutes
to get through airport security.
(Howard:)Look. I made Sheldon disappear.
Ta-da!
(Leonard:)Next time you should open with that.